[{"answer": " When", "docId": "Bodies_-Rest-&-Motion.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "In two days?", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": " Hi", "docId": "Bodies_-Rest-&-Motion.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "Hi", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": " I, umm... I... It embarrasses me. When you talk about something with my friend that happened before me. She's my best friend. It embarrasses me that you used to live with her", "docId": "Bodies_-Rest-&-Motion.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "Three years", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "I don't know why we're even bothering to pack", "docId": "Bodies_-Rest-&-Motion.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "The t.v. gets no channels", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": " my friend.  The man I live with", "docId": "Bodies_-Rest-&-Motion.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "He'd find us. And he'd be surprised", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "my friend's gonna steal a t.v", "docId": "Bodies_-Rest-&-Motion.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "I've never heard that expression", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "It's not a crime", "docId": "Bodies_-Rest-&-Motion.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "Poetic justice", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "I also mow lawns", "docId": "Bodies_-Rest-&-Motion.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "Painting. I'm an inside person.  Mowing grass is seasonal", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "It makes teevee seem very futuristic", "docId": "Bodies_-Rest-&-Motion.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "I'm hardly stoned", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "No", "docId": "Bodies_-Rest-&-Motion.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "I lost mine one at a time.  Last year", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": " Have you ever been in a relationship", "docId": "Bodies_-Rest-&-Motion.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": " You weren't married..", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "I see the lawns I mow, houses I've painted, faces I know... my parents... And I'm constantly reminded of who I am", "docId": "Bodies_-Rest-&-Motion.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "I want you", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "Yes", "docId": "Bodies_-Rest-&-Motion.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": " I want... I want..", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": " I'd be so much happier if I could blame this on my friend, but it always happens to me. I'm always left with nothing.  It doesn't matter if I leave the guy or if the guy leaves me", "docId": "Bodies_-Rest-&-Motion.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "No...  He didn't take 'em. I mean, when he cared about me, he cared about me. And he was really good in bed", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": "So what are you gonna do", "docId": "Bodies_-Rest-&-Motion.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": "I've got some", "qsentId": 30}, {"answer": " Okay..", "docId": "Bodies_-Rest-&-Motion.txt", "asentId": 33, "question": "Let's do things, get you busy", "qsentId": 32}, {"answer": "I meet men, go home with them and just stay. No decision involved", "docId": "Bodies_-Rest-&-Motion.txt", "asentId": 35, "question": "What way are we", "qsentId": 34}, {"answer": " That's what makes you an adult", "docId": "Bodies_-Rest-&-Motion.txt", "asentId": 37, "question": " You can say no to me", "qsentId": 36}, {"answer": "Shit", "docId": "Bodies_-Rest-&-Motion.txt", "asentId": 39, "question": " I got that. Where'd she go", "qsentId": 38}, {"answer": " You left her", "docId": "Bodies_-Rest-&-Motion.txt", "asentId": 41, "question": " You didn't find anyone", "qsentId": 40}, {"answer": "Cause you fucked her? No! That gives you no business in my life", "docId": "Bodies_-Rest-&-Motion.txt", "asentId": 43, "question": "Be glad you have a home, asshole", "qsentId": 42}, {"answer": "It wasn't offered", "docId": "Bodies_-Rest-&-Motion.txt", "asentId": 45, "question": "You can't take another person. They have to give themselves to you", "qsentId": 44}, {"answer": " You start driving east on route forty. Keep going east and around eleven start checking every roadside motel. The budget ones... You do that all night, you'll find her", "docId": "Bodies_-Rest-&-Motion.txt", "asentId": 47, "question": "When you don't know where you're going, you drive on the highway", "qsentId": 46}, {"answer": "You just can't do it", "docId": "Bodies_-Rest-&-Motion.txt", "asentId": 49, "question": " Okay", "qsentId": 48}]